|||||\\\\\\\\\\\\\
Alchemy
Shower
I forbid anyone to open this gate
Stay where you are!
You can't just leave
What about the child?
Think about what they'll say about Do Hwa and that baby
They will gossip that the son is not yours,
that he is illegitimate
He will have the surname Chan since my wife gave birth to him.
I'll send someone to pick him up after the funeral
Are you leaving him?
He's true
not your son?
Believe what you want
If he's nothing but problems,
let's get rid of it here and now
Do you see? He is your son
The son you want to protect even at the cost of your life
I'm just trying to keep him safe
If his energy gates are not opened and he lives like my son, he will survive
But if he decides to try his luck,
death awaits him
Who is the father
child?
His father is dead
His birth has no meaning, moreover,
he shouldn't have been born at all
Project coordinator and editor: Ria_Lee
Assistant coordinators: Sana, Martini
Young Master, are you okay?
Typesetter translators: Ria_Lee, tommo
Why did you release her?
Let her go
Sorry for causing trouble
Why did you untie her?
She tried to poison you
She didn't try
I drank the poison myself
Because I couldn't cast spells
My maid only did what she was told. At the cost of his life
I ordered her
- Chan Wook, how could you?
- Wait with this
He hasn't fully recovered yet
Punish him as you wish, but after he recovers
Uk almost died
No need to scold him
He's all pale
Take him home bye
Mister, let's go
Go to Sejukwon, they will cure you there
Moo Deok needs to go there too
Now is not the time...
Moo Deok needs treatment too
Otherwise I won't go
Mister!
Well, great! Die then
- Lock them up again!
- Uncle, calm down
If Wook is telling the truth, it's not her fault.
She is seriously injured
Without treatment she will die
I'm surprised she's still alive after all the beatings.
If she dies, I'll let you conduct her funeral.
Please help
Moo Deok risked her life to carry out my orders.
She must be taken to Sejukwon, otherwise she will not survive.
Help her
Get them out of my sight
Take them to Saejukwon
Uk...
Young master, go ahead. I'll bring Moo Deok
Moo Deok
Moo Deok, wake up
- I'll carry her
- No
I myself
You can't even stand on your feet
I can do it. She's my maid, I'll carry her myself
You can barely walk on your own
You can't get it there
Do you think so? Then...
- You will carry her on your back
- What?
Come on
- Do you want me to carry it?
- Yes
Why me?
- Come here
- Young Master
No. Wait. Heaven...
Holy heavens
Hey Yul. Listen...
Carry me instead of Moo Deok
I have no strength at all. Take me to Sejukwon
Do you want me to carry him?
- No
- Okay, thank you
Maid Kim, be careful!
- Be careful with her
- Okay
- Well...
- What...
Caution
As a result, Uk
opened the gates of energy
Yes
He risked his life. I couldn't just sit and watch
I think he understood
that we won't let him kill himself
He probably drank the poison himself,
so that we save him
Is everything okay?
Opening the Uka Gate and treating it
probably cost me ten years of energy
So you not only opened his gates, but also gave him energy?
What should I, an old man, store my energy for?
He was poisoned
so I gave him the strength to recover quickly
When Uk is restored, you must return them
Is this really necessary when his gates are open?
He was 20 years late in learning spells
Even if he starts studying now,
learn something worthwhile by age 60
This is his destiny
We need to make sure of this
If you want it, I'll take the strength
You know what?
I'm too tired. I want to relax
Bring me some wine
Guilt?
That is...
Where does the wine in the practice room come from?
I saw
I saw that you kept it in yourself
Come on. The wine you drink when you're lonely
- I'm not alone!
- That's right
I'm completely...
Head hurts
This is because...
What was it called?
Exactly. Insomnia
I have terrible insomnia
I drink wine for insomnia
Loneliness keeps you from sleeping
You should have married in your youth
Have you forgotten Do Hwa yet? So lonely?
It's empty here
- What?
- You drank it all
It can't be. What?
What...
I think you were incredibly lonely
I only drank one drink when I couldn't sleep
Just one drink each time...
This is the wine that my uncle hid in his place
Tastes good
Finally, Uka's lifelong dream came true
Let's celebrate
That girl, Moo Deok...
He recently brought her from the gisaeng house, right?
She risked her life for him, even though they had just met.
This is weird
Wook saved her from becoming a gisaeng
She didn't want it so much that she pretended to be blind
Drink
"Blind"?
Yes. According to Joo Wol, she was blind when she arrived,
and as soon as I left there, I immediately saw the light
The wine is wonderful
She deceives people easily
She lied that she was blind and that she poisoned Uka
She remained silent despite the torture
There's more to her than meets the eye
Outwardly she is a sweet and naive girl
But she's clearly hiding something
- You drank it all
- What? What are you talking about?
Your uncle is coming here
I think you're doomed
- I didn't drink anything
- Wait, Yul
Yul!
- Mommies
- Dan Gu
I'm finished
Park Dan Goo
Is that you?
No
Come here
- Dan Gu
- Yes, uncle?
Is she breathing?
Woke up
You didn't come to your senses, you thought you might die
Does it hurt?
I think my bones are broken
Nothing's broken
- Really?
- Yes
Then why does it hurt so much?
Useless body
Hey
Why did you say you poisoned me?
If you pretended you didn't know anything,
you wouldn't be tortured
To make them believe that you are dying
Otherwise they wouldn't have opened your gates
Let's make an antidote
So you really risked your life
I thought they would cut off my arm or leg
But I'm fine
The people of Sosnovy Bor are too kind
If they torture people like that...
And you...
You look pretty sick
Why are you here?
Obviously, to take care of you
All students here are magicians
They shouldn't know about you
So I closed the door while no one was looking
changed your clothes, applied ointment to your wounds
I even gave you a massage when you lost consciousness
- Really?
- Yes
Only you can let me get so close to you
For my whole life
no one understood how desperate I was
And no one risked their life for me,
except you
Since I survived as promised,
I will treat you like a master
I have already changed 12 masters
Everyone thinks the teachers abandoned me, but it was me who left.
And now I have found a true teacher
So I must get on my knees
and swear that I will always treat you like a teacher
On one condition
Don't tell anyone about our relationship
You will remain my master
and I'm your maid
And also,
our master-student relationship will last until you become the best
and help me get my energy back
Until then
When I get my power back and become Nak Soo,
we won't be master and student
Why is this?
Then
you won't have to protect me anymore
and I don't have to be
soft with you
Do you want to leave me when this is all over?
I see
Okay
You'll leave me when you don't need me anymore
Then I will respect your decision and let you go
And now kneel before the master
I, Chan Wook, your student,
I will serve and protect my master Moo Deok
You've got your look back
You won't go wild for a while
Then meet me at the palace
Feed the soul swallower with human souls,
so that he is useful
You killed the gisaeng into whose body Nak Soo escaped
Yes. We dumped the body in Gyeongjeongdaeho Lake
Have you checked for the blue mark?
No tag
This is not Nak Soo
Yes, I checked
The Nak Soo I knew wouldn't lose to you
but she apparently lost her strength
Can nomads lose strength?
If a strong soul
falls into the wrong body and is unable to access its power
Have you seen this before?
Your Majesty,
I am Jin Mu, Master Chan's student
I heard you asking me
Jin Mu
Yes
I'm not a king. It's me, Chang Gang
The soul of the king is now in my body
Master, is that you?
Yes, the king and I switched bodies
Then where is His Majesty?
His soul is in my body
I have to get my body back
But I can't use my strength
I need your help
Master
I don't know how soul alchemy works
Go to Jeonbugwan's secret hall and bring back the Soul Reflector
I will teach you the alchemy of souls
He could not regain his strength due to his weak body,
so I got a chance
I'm lucky
Burn all these bodies
Search the gisaeng house where the murdered woman worked.
Find the owner of the spirit amulet
The main thing is unnoticed
Yes
What are you doing?
It's cold
The water is absolutely freezing
Of course it's cold. Why are you sitting there?
This is the first time I feel such cold
I've passed out before because the energy gate was closed
And now, even though I’m shaking, I can stand
So my gates are indeed open
If you master the spells, it won't be cold even on ice
And the fire won't burn
What were you like before you changed your body?
There were a lot of rumors about you
But I've never seen you
I heard you were strong
Not just strong, but very strong
"Very"? I see
To become a better magician, you need to go through several stages
First Chipsu, the ability to harness water energy
Second step - Ryusu, the ability to control the energy of water flow
Then Chisu - control of water energy
in the atmosphere
I mastered all three stages
Few people in Deho are capable of this
Master, you live up to your name
Yes
I moved silently, like a shadow,
and the heads of my enemies fell to the ground as I passed by
I was Nak Soo
shadow warrior
I walked on water as if I was flying
Where will I go - the wind rose
And I’ll do this - it was raining
I am Nak Soo, the best magician in the world,
who can create snow and rain
Are you okay?
Just a couple of moves
and your lungs are ready to explode
What is it?
My leg cramped!
Spasm?
These legs are short, thin, weak and cannot stand the cold
Useless body
Be careful. You are no longer Nak Soo, the shadow warrior.
You are Moo Deok, my maid
Don't jump around like you are now
You'll get hurt
I feel like nothing
Don't be sad. You have me
Let's start training, my gates are open
But first, put on your shoes. It's cold
For what?
No agility
Pick up
What are you doing?
Let's see how good my student is, then I will forget about sadness
What?
Why beat?
You don't wield a sword
Show me how you fight
Here's a small one...
It hurts!
You fight badly too
You're worse than I thought
I never really studied!
You had 12 teachers
You haven't learned how to cast spells,
but could learn martial arts
I didn't have the mood for it
As you know
I need to get ready to do anything
You're just lazy
I noticed that you don't do anything at home
Yes, I learned everything by heart. Check
Do you think I recognized you?
I realized that you are using Tansu style
Just chatter
I can do more than just talk
Did you see it?
I'm a fast learner
I will quickly master Chipsa. How long does it take?
I'm a fast learner too, but it took me five years
And for others - 20 years
And you...
Maybe you'll master it even faster,
since you are Chang Gan's son
And what side is he here?
He's a genius who mastered Chipsu in a year
You will master Chipsa in a year,
rumors that you are not his son will subside
But of course this is hardly possible
If it took him a year, I will master it in six months
No, in three months
Talking again
I'm determined, don't knock me down
Maid Kim told me to sweep the whole yard
You've gotten better
Yes, and you are doing well, so help me
What...
Moo Deok...
I'm a lazy person who doesn't do anything without the right attitude.
Good luck
Bastard...
- Well...
- It's so cool
Useless lazy fellow!
So cool, even cold
Master Ho made medicine for Wook
Apparently it's very effective
Especially when its gates are open
Maid Kim, you seem very pleased
Are you so upset that his gates are open?
You did nothing even when he was dying
If it weren't for Master Huo, the young master might have died
He had to find a way to save him without opening the gate
How harmful you are
You always kept your distance from the young master
This...
because of rumors?
What rumors?
Don't pretend you don't know
You know there are rumors
that you are Mr. Chan's father
Don't you dare mention
such absurd rumors!
They're not that absurd
Let's be honest, we both know
that you loved Ms. Do Hwa before she got married
You wrote her poems and gave her gifts
I'm a living witness
They say you still haven't gotten married because you haven't forgotten her
What about you, Maid Kim?
Are you still in love with Chang Gang?
Is that why you didn't get married and live in his house?
What?
I know how much you liked him
When he told you he liked acorn jelly,
you climbed to the top of the mountain like a squirrel,
- to collect acorns
- Squirrel?
I saw you collecting acorns
So what?
Are you laughing at the fact that I went out collecting acorns?
Yes!
I admit that I went to collect them
I could only express my feelings by making this jelly
You can laugh at me all you want
I'm not laughing
When I saw you making this jelly,
I felt sad
I know what it's like
when you can't do anything
for the person you love
Others
may speak evil of us behind our backs
But let's not do this to each other
It's obvious that the love we felt
when we were young
ended up leaving a scar in our hearts
I was on edge because of Mr. Chan.
and said too much
Forgive me
I'm really worried about Uka
I'm just afraid that if I open the gates of energy,
we could break the barrier that protected him
I'm uneasy about this
I may have to suppress his will
and stop in the future
Please don't despise me for this
Let's see how everything turns out
Sir, this is wild ginseng tea
Drink it
Wild ginseng?
I'll have a drink when I get back. Leave it here
you again
want to give it to Moo Deok?
It's cold outside. She deserves something warm and nice
Why did you make her sweep the yard in such cold weather?
Listen
This maid was cured for free
So I asked her to do something in return.
Why her? Couldn't you do it yourself?
I needed to brew some medicine for you, cook dinner
and take care of you
Moo Deok will take care of me. You don't need to worry
Clear
You're only worried about Moo Deok
Since I've become useless
I'll go sweep the yard like Moo Deok
I just feel like I've put too much on you
How long have you been brewing this wild ginseng?
I cooked it all day
That's what I'm talking about. You couldn't even close your eyes
How do you think this makes me feel?
- Not good
- Exactly
I know you've been through a lot because of me
And he looks tired. You used to have porcelain skin
You should drink wild ginseng tea
Maybe then you'll stop getting into trouble?
I don't know what to tell the boss
I will accept his punishment
Now my gates are open, which means I will become part of Sosnovy Bor
Are you so happy that the gate is open?
Yes, very much
When I enter Sosnovy Bor and become better than Yulia and Dan Gu,
they will regret not accepting me sooner
Maid Kim, you can eat this ginseng
Thanks for the ginseng, I really appreciate it
You must be that evil maid
What are you doing? We gave you medicine
You might catch the disease
I was cured for free
so they said I should work to show my gratitude
Maid Kim is a wise woman
Sweep the yard, then bring fertilizer to the herb garden
Yes
Just wait, Ho Yeom
Now I'm sweeping your yard
but one day I will get rid of Saejukwon
Hey! Watch where you're aiming
Did you do this on purpose?
No
And I think so
How dare I
You are very strange
These ears...
I've seen them before
Haven't I treated you in the past?
Where do I get the money to get treatment in Sejukwon?
These ears look familiar
Sweep thoroughly
He almost tore my ear off
I know you're hurting, but just be patient.
He's angry at Mr. Chan so he takes it out on you
It’s normal to bully the weak, that’s how the world works.
I'll just keep quiet
Try not to hate him
He gave away the flow of energy that cost him ten years,
to help the young master recover faster
Rest when you're done
Energy flow of ten years?
What took you so long?
Come here, this is wild ginseng...
What is it, Moo Deok?
What are you doing?
Stand still
That's not why I brought you here
Moo Deok, this is wrong. I'm your student, stop it
That's it
What are you doing?
I'm testing the core of your energy
Breathe calmly
Here it is
There is truth
You are truly special
Stop it
What's inside of me?
Incredible flow of energy
Ho Yeom put energy into you
Energy?
It seems that Uk has already recovered
It's time to extract the energy you put into it.
If things go wrong, he might lose his mind.
Uk won't be able to use it
The gates of his energy have just opened
There's really nothing he can do
You're worrying in vain
Most likely he doesn’t even know that there is something so incredible inside him
Let's steal Ho Yeom's energy
The core of your energy is filled with the energy that Ho Yeom gave you
Now you are strong enough to easily use Chipsa
I had no idea that there was something so valuable in me
It takes ten years to collect that kind of energy, but you got it for free.
Besides, this is Ho Yeom's energy, you can't ask for anything better
You're a lucky fool
I thought the old man hated me. I'm surprised he gave it to me
He gave it to you to help you get better.
He'll pick her up soon
He can't do that. What's in my belly is mine
If you don't have the strength to control her,
your strength will disappear and he will take it away
I have to learn to control the energy so I can keep it for myself.
So I have to breathe as a source of energy
I guess these 12 teachers taught you something at least
You're right
Energy from the core is controlled by breathing,
however, all magicians breathe differently
Everyone inhales and exhales different amounts of air.
This is Ho Yeom's energy, so you need to control it with his breath
I doubt he'll teach me
Maybe we should just try everything? It's just breathing
If you use someone's breath, you can lose control and go crazy
Blood will flow from every part of your body and you will die.
Well, shall we try?
No
You go to extremes
Teacher, come up with a way that will keep me alive and allow me to control energy
Basic breathing techniques are passed down from generation to generation.
Ho Yeom from the Seo family
This means that any member of the So family will use the same technique
- Seo Yul
Go ask him. You said you were close
Yul is cautious
If I ask, he will understand and tell Ho Yeom
Just ten breaths...
No, seven will be enough
I can understand by placing my hand on the core of his energy
He'll break your arm before he takes a breath.
You're right, he's not like you
Me?
What's wrong with me?
What? What kind of contemptuous look is this?
Anyway, I don't think I can do to him what I did to you.
No no, Moo Deok
Look me in the eyes
It’s inconvenient for you to touch him, but with me for once or twice?
Like a child. Is this important now?
Child?
Yes, very important
Are you crazy? What are you doing?
I'm in perfect health
- No, let's say that I'm crazy
- Well, let me go
What are you doing here?
Hello
Why do you always bully Moo Deok?
She hasn't recovered yet
I didn't mock her
- What?
- Here's a beetle
I thought you were kind
Moo Deok, are you okay?
Your master is asking too much of you, isn't he?
Not only do you take care of him, but also entertain him
He asks for warm water, but when I bring it,
asks for a cold one again...
- Hey, what...
- He says the food is salty,
but then complains that she is bland
- Me?
- He is immature and moody
Lazy but with high self-esteem
But what can I do?
He is my master
so I have to serve him
Moo Deok, it seems you managed to learn a lot about him
I'm ashamed of you
By the way, what are you doing here? Why aren't you in Sejukwon?
We came to Yul
Moo Deok asked me to come
Yul?
Why don't you approach him then?
We spied on him
Moo Deok was embarrassed to approach him,
that's why I stayed with her
Moo Deok, you probably like Yul
- No...
- Dan Gu,
you pick up on everything quickly
I'm already embarrassed
- Master! There was a misunderstanding
- Don't be shy
Many girls like Yul
- Your feelings are normal
- This is not...
I will help Moo Deok
Uk, go to the reception
Why?
Master Huo wants to see you
Master Huo?
I heard you calling me
Yes
The sound of your cough is pleasant and clear
I think you feel much better
I'm still dizzy and nauseous
Plus I'm losing consciousness
But thanks to you I'm getting better
I saw you and your maid
had fun walking this morning
Isn't it strange?
Hey, come on, stand here
I need to take something from you
But first
I brought something for you
For me?
As a child
I let a flock of sheep into your herb garden
I know you hate me ever since
Those sheep ate medicinal herbs
and live to this day
Despite this, you saved my life
and allowed to live. I am deeply grateful to you for this
I thought you were a real idiot
but it seems you have learned to show gratitude
I have prepared something for you
Maid Kim
This wine is made from meltwater from Volcano Island in South Daeho.
The best dark wine in Daeho
The gentleman said that he wanted to thank you,
so I had to put in a lot of effort to get it
This is a rare delicacy
Is there only one bottle?
You definitely know a lot about gratitude!
Maid Kim, you raised him well
Thank you
Bring it here, quickly
What a joy
Three bottles?
Mother
The gates of Uka energy have opened
Up to this point, we couldn't do anything because of the Gwangju order.
Does this mean that we can now accept him into the family?
This guy broke off his engagement after using you
And do you still love him?
I used it for my own purposes
The gate of his energy was closed and I used it against him,
forcing him to live with us
Don't twist the truth
He said that he would live with us if we help him open the gates of energy
That's how he seduced you
In the end it happened
If you had opened its gates then,
you would have a son-in-law
and I would marry whoever I want
Cho Young
The son of the Chan family, whose gate of energy is open,
will never be my son-in-law
You should take your sister's place
and become the head who protects Jinyeowon for the sake of the family
Find a man who will support you
If my sister hadn't died,
I would marry my beloved
Sorry mom
Check whether Gwiga's urn has been collected or not
Okay
Uk broke Gwiga's urn
What if I ask him to marry me in return?
He will definitely refuse
Does Mr. Yul sleep in the farthest room?
Yes, he loves peace and quiet
When does he go to bed?
If he's not busy,
goes to bed early and gets up early
What?
Do you want to visit his bedroom?
No matter how much you like him, it's wrong
Hint
He always eats at the same time, you can see him at lunch
Okay
I need more than to see. I need to touch it
We're Doc, are you okay?
Yul...
Outsiders are not allowed to read books in Jeongjingak
She only helps
Yes, and spells are written in them
She still won't understand
And you're smart
Do you know martial arts?
I learned to dance in the gisaeng house
That's why I'm fast
Where's Don Yi? Gotta ask something
Dong Yi is not here, but Moo Deok is
Moo Deok, help him
I'll help
No need
Help, young master?
Sir, are you hungry? What to bring?
Sir, I...
The magicians of Chongjingak live here. Don't follow me
If he goes to bed early, it means he's going to bed.
Is this the restroom?
I told you to leave. Why are you here?
I thought maybe I could help with something
to you
do you need something from me?
Just touch you. And this is a chance
Why did you follow me all the way to the men's room?
This is my chance. Six breaths and I will understand how he breathes
One
Two
Three
Four
Why did you do this?
I was so close
I know that you and Uk were looking at me from afar
Why are you following me?
Just one breath
Answer
I love you!
Are you okay?
It hurts
You are interested in my breathing technique. Trying to reach the core of my energy
I'm telling you, I love you
You lie so skillfully
And earlier it was not dance, but martial arts
My life was hard
so I learned a couple of moves for safety's sake
Is this for Uka?
I think he's trying to control the energy inside
But he can't succeed even with my technique.
Stop wasting time. Get better and go away
So do you remember me
Yul
I didn't ignore you because I hated you
Your mom Do Hwa was like a daughter to me
I'm someone like your grandfather
Juvenile scoundrel
Yes, grandpa
Your mother was very kind
Really?
Yes! You should know this
Remember this and don’t pay attention to other people’s words
This poor child...
Length and depth of inhalations and exhalations
It's hard to play. I'm impressed
I can do a lot
Give it back
He seems to be many years old
Why do you need something so old?
It belongs to an old friend
Instead of a friend nearby, you have a whistle
It means your friend left you
Yes
This belongs to that friend
Give me back, he means a lot to me
In return, teach me your breathing technique.
You said it's no use anyway
This is also useless to me
Let's change
To me it's trash
I can break it
Just three breaths
Where is she?
What's that facial expression?
Doesn't look like you
I like him
You've got it all twisted up like that
I followed Yul and repeated that I liked him, and now I found out
I see
You are a sensitive person who kills everyone in your path,
but I decided to flirt with the guy for the sake of my student
What about you?
I hope you didn't let Ho Yeom take away his energy
The strength is in me. And I learned his breathing technique
So you wasted your time
Did you find out? Don't lie to me
I'm sure you're lying
to pretend that you did something worthwhile
I was breathing like this. how is he
And I think I felt something moving inside me
Energy is boiling inside you
It worked
Were you that close to Yul?
Carefully. I still see the mark in your eyes
I used eye drops
I didn't see the mark in the mirror. You can see it, right?
This is how you look
If you really like him, this is how you should approach him
Be careful with love
Only I can be allowed to do this
Okay. Now only you can
I'll try not to fall in love with Yulia
What?
Why does this take effort?
He's handsome
It takes effort not to fall in love with a handsome man
What about me?
I think it was much more difficult not to fall in love with me
Not at all
Why not? It doesn't make sense
- Say it was difficult
- Yes, master
- Tell me seriously
- Yes
- Are you going to say that?
Come on, make me laugh
Your Highness
Judging by the energy on your sword,
you have mastered the highest degree of Ryusu
All thanks to you
Gyeongju's deputy
The only one who can compete with you
I think only Seo Yul is from the Seo family
Her Majesty the Queen and Julia's father, General So, brother and sister
Yul and I were very close as children,
but everything changed when he entered Sosnovy Bor
Seo Yul, Park Dan Gu, Chan Wook and Jin Cho Young are famous
like Four Seasons
Let them have fun
Wait a minute
Why is Chan Wook also among them when he doesn’t have magic?
Now owns
His gates of energy are open
Is the gate open?
But there's only so much he can do
He is the son of Jang Gang, Gwangju Jeonbugwan
Recently
he came and asked about Nak Su's sword
And?
Are you afraid that I will succeed?
So did you give it away?
His Majesty ordered you to keep it in Jeonbugwan
Gwangju Post belongs to the Jang family
There was no choice
How rude
He looks down on me
Still, I was his father's student
Come to think of it, I wasn't officially his student
I had nowhere to go when the Jin family threw me out,
he took me as a servant
You are the teacher of the Crown Prince of this country
How dare he?
It's like looking down on me
I apologize for
that your teacher does not come from a noble family
We need it soon
put Chan Wook in his place
This is the sword of Gwangju Chan, to Chan Wook's father
I somehow...
promised to accept him if he exposed
his father's sword
Now the gates of his energy are open and it is possible
Will you allow him to become the magician of Sosnovy Bor?
Bring Uka
What did you say? Who is his father?
The deceased king
He is the king's son!
So he is the king's son,
who died a year ago?
The deceased king
died due to illness without being able to move
How is this possible?
On this baby's birthday,
the king's new star shone in the sky
The brother of the deceased king has already taken the throne,
which his son will inherit
If the royal family finds out that this is the king's son,
he will be perceived
as a threat
His existence will bring chaos
He shouldn't attract attention to himself
People must think there is nothing unusual about him
I sincerely apologize
for all the problems I created
Sosnovy Bor decided
open the gates of your energy,
so you are not responsible
I, Chan Wook, the eldest son of the Chan family,
ready to learn and practice
If Sosnovy Bor gives me a chance, I will do my best
As a sign of your loyalty,
I will give you the sword Nak Soo took from Jin Mu,
so that it is stored in the Sosnovy Bor armory
No need
The sword belongs to the Chan family, let it be kept by you
You can take your father's sword
From now on, I forbid Chan Wook from entering Sosnovy Bor
You are free to come
like the son of an old friend
But you do not have the right to become a magician of Sosnovy Bor
Now
Chan Wook will not have access to anything in the forest
Give me the amulet that allows you to pass here
I don't have it
What?
I'm lost
spirit amulet
What punishment is provided for those
who will lose the amulet?
Spanking, 100 strokes, master
Then I give Chan Wook a hundred blows
for the loss of the amulet
He has the energy of Master Huo, everything will be fine
If you get in, he'll have more problems.
Chan Wook, leave Sosnovy Bor
and don't come here again
Go away
No
No...
I can't leave like this
I've been hit 99 times
One hit left
And this last one
apply it yourself
I'm just trying to keep him safe
If his energy gates are not opened and he lives like my son, he will survive
But if he decides to try his luck,
death awaits him
Uk, just give up
and live quietly
This is the only way you will survive
Moo Deok,
take the sword
We're leaving
/////////////////////////////////////
Thanks for watching with us!
Space for your advertising
Alchemy
Shower
I want to bare it and show them
- Is this a sign of stupidity?
- No, strength
Stand your ground
There is another sword that you cannot draw
But it belongs to his father
I have to pick him up
Whoever wins takes it
Going against the prince is a sign of stupidity
But some believe it is a show of strength. I have to try
My student is too weak to fight against you
He needs to be put in danger again
And he'll get what he wants